(Sheldon:)He's not just a middle child,
he is the quintessential middle child.
(Sheldon:)From a broken home, to boot.
Psychologically speaking...
(Sheldon:)...the attention he gets by rebelling,
even to the point of destruction...
(Sheldon:)...is more emotionally valuable
than help he would get at rehab.
- I've got a solution.
- Great. What is it?
(Leonard:)Get out.
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)I've hesitated to point this out...
...but I must remind you
we are in our predicament...
(Sheldon:)...because of your initial
and inadequate deceit.
(Sheldon:)I'm just trying to clean up
after your mess.
SHELDON:
We'll talk in the morning.
(Leonard:)Morning.
(Leonard:)Who are you?
(Man:)I am Sheldon's cousin Leo.